It's a fawn!
小鹿だ
本字幕由✿花語&花丸字幕組✿共同製作
よく捕まえたね
Nice catch.
抱えて飛ぶのがちょっと大変だったけどね
Flying with it was a bit difficult.
ジェハの足って本当に凄いわ
Your legs are amazing, Jae-ha.
We should find the Yellow Dragon in no time.
これなら黄龍だってすぐに見つけられそう
あぁ そういえば後は黄龍だけなんだっけ
Yeah. The Yellow Dragon's the last one, right?
ここまで来たら 顔を拝むのも悪くないか
After coming this far,
I wouldn't mind seeing his face.
I'll find him.
探してあげよう
いや その役名は私が
No, I will.
No, let me handle this.
今日のところは僕が
No, I'm much better at searching for dragons!
いや 龍探しに関しては私が
Let's just take our time.
まぁ 焦らず行こう
俺 御飯の支度してくる
I'm going to prepare dinner.
雷獸は火を起こしといて
Thunder Beast, start a fire.
Okay.
Episode 24:          From Now On
Yona, you don't mind butchering animals anymore?
ヨナ 捌くの平気になったの
まだちょっと辛いけど
It's still a little hard.
城に居た頃は
When I lived in the castle, I didn't think about how we were taking living creatures' lives.
生き物の命を頂くということ 何も感じていなかったの
Turning away would mean ignoring
that this fawn was alive.
目をそらすということは
この子に命があることを無視することなんだわ
Growl
Grumble
Gurgle
や 娘さん 立派 立派
I'm impressed, miss.
Huh?
But all living things return to heaven one day.
でも命あるもの いつかは等しく天に帰る
娘さんは手合わせて感謝してんだ
You were expressing your gratitude.
此奴だって許してくれるさ
I'm sure it will forgive you.
涎垂れてるよ
You're drooling.
腹鳴ってるよ
Your stomach's growling.
ってか 誰
Who are you, anyway?
Growl
気にしなくていいから
Don't worry about that.
Growl
ただの通りすがりだから
I'm just a passerby.
Growl
涎はいつも垂れ流しだから
And I'm always drooling.
Growl
拭けよ
Wipe your mouth!
Growl
なんか美味そうな匂いがしたんで来ちゃった
I came because I smelled something yummy.
まだ生臭い臭いしかしてないよ
It still just smells bloody.
お腹空いてるの
Are you hungry?
尋常じゃなく減ってるから
Extraordinarily hungry.
美味そう
Oh? That looks good.
今日はモリモリ食べていいよ
You can gorge yourselves today.
Nice. We haven't had meat in a while.
嬉しいね 久々の肉だ
By the way...
ところで
Munch
誰 あいつ
Who is he?
Munch
なんか 旅の人 俺も分かんない
A traveler, I guess. I'm not sure.
お腹空いてたみたいだから 呼んだの
He seemed hungry, so we invited him.
ところでキジャ 黄龍について情報とかないの
By the way, Ki-ja, do you know anything about the Yellow Dragon?
どこに住んでるとか 特徴とかさ
Where he lives or about his traits?
According to the founding myth,
he has a "strong body."
建国神話によると 確か頑丈な体を持つ者よね
Maybe he's covered in hard scales.
体が硬い鱗で出来てんのかな
Or he's a big, burly man.
ごっつい大男とか
ちょっとそこ こっち来て食べなよ
Hey, you guys. Come over here and eat.
そなた どう思う
What do you think?
Most likely.
かなり間違いなく
Huh? What is it?
なに どうしたの
なんていうかさ
Well, actually...
I think that kid eating meat over there...
さっきからそこで肉食べてる子なんだけど
is the Yellow Dragon.
黄龍だと思うよ
Huh?
呼んだ
Hm? Did you call me?
あれ よく見ると 白龍 青龍 緑龍までいる
Hey, I see you've got the White, Blue, and Green Dragons with you.
Well, well.
これはこれは 皆さんお揃いで
Bow
The gang's all here.
Whaaat?!
What?!
Yellow Dragon?
黄龍？
You mean the Yellow Dragon?
黄龍ってあの黄龍
Why? Why is he here?
どうして どうしているの
Why is he eating meat with us as if it's no big deal?
なぜ普通に焼肉の宴に参加しているのだ
皆落ち着きないな
You guys need to relax.
ゼノはちゃんと座って食べてる 偉くなぇ？
Zeno sits like a good boy when he eats. See?
ゼノって 俺の名前だから
Oh, Zeno's my name.
なにそのグダグダな自己紹介
What kind of self-introduction was that?
黄龍が近くにいる気はしていたが
I sensed the Yellow Dragon nearby,
but he seemed so close, I doubted myself.
近すぎて逆疑ってしまった
I know what you mean.
あるよね
You didn't notice that we were nearby?
君は気づかなかったのかい 僕らが近くいすこと
I don't care either way.
気づくとか気づかないとか
ゼノはのんびり旅してるだけだから
I'm just wandering around.
他の龍とかあんまり気にしない
I'm not concerned with the other dragons.
Huh...
気にしない？
Not concerned?
Huh...
Despite all you said, you seemed really concerned with the other dragons.
お前 なんだかんだで他の龍気にしまくってたもんな
Your claws are stabbing me,
White Snake.
Zeno, you don't feel anything
when you look at her?
Your claws are stabbing me,
White Snake.
ゼノとやら 其方こちらのお方を見て何も感じぬのか
Your claws are stabbing me,
White Snake.
Sha-zing
This is Princess Yona!
ヨナ姫様だ
Sha-zing
われわれ四龍の主であらせられる
Master of the four dragons!
Sha-zing
まだそんな大げさな...
You're exaggerating again.
Sha-zing
姫様
Princess...
主
Master...
何も感じないなんて失礼な
It's pretty rude of you to say I don't feel anything.
娘さんは超可愛いから
She's really cute.
ドキドキだから
My heart is pounding.
そんなことは知っている
I know that!
That isn't what I meant!
そうではなくて
まさか其方 あの洗礼を感じなかったのか
Did you not feel that awakening?
この僕でさえ もう煮るなり抱くなり好きにしてとなったあの洗礼を
It had even me saying,
"Boil me, take me, do as you please."
どんな洗礼だよ
What kind of awakening is that?
大物か よっぽと鈍感なのか
Is he strong or just really dense?
Rumble
でも 一人で気ままに旅してるなら あれかな
But since you're traveling alone, maybe...
どれかな
Maybe what?
仲間になってほしいってお願いは難しいかな
Would it be difficult for you
to do us the favor of joining us?
私達四龍を探して力を貸して貰ってるんだけど貴方にも...
We've been looking for the four dragons and asking for their help, so I'd like you to-
Sure.
いいよ
Huh?
Okay.
I'm just wandering around.
ゼノは好きに旅してるだけだから
特に目的地とかないし 暇だし
I don't have a destination or anything to do.
何より 御飯超美味しかったから
Above all, the food was great.
Showing my gratitude for good food is my hobby!
食べ物の恩は大事にする趣味
主義だろう
You mean principle.
よろしくね
Nice to meet you.
そして明日からも美味しい御飯よろしくね
I look forward to more great meals
from tomorrow onward.
なんという
Unbelievable.
ふらふらやってきて最速で仲間に
He wandered in and joined us fastest of all.
単に飢えてたからじゃないの
Maybe he was just starving.
白蛇の最速記録を塗り替えたな
He broke your record for speed of joining, White Snake.
兄ちゃんもよろしくね
Nice to meet you too.
黄龍ゼノよ
Yellow Dragon Zeno...
Huh?
私は白龍キジャ
I am the White Dragon, Ki-ja.
右手に龍の力を宿す者
I possess the dragon's power in my right hand.
其方も我々と共に姫様をお守りするのならば
If you wish to protect the princess with us, show us your power.
その力を示せ
力
My power?
Yes.
そうだ
My power...
ゼノ力はあんまないけど 体は丈夫
I'm not too strong, but my body's real tough.
やはりそうか
So it's true.
どのくらい丈夫なんだ
How tough?
That hurt you?
痛いのかよ
体弱いじゃん 普通の人じゃん
You're weak! You're a normal person!
Are you really the Yellow Dragon?!
あんた本当に黄龍
No, there's just something wrong with him!
いやいやその兄ちゃんおかしいから
His arms are ridiculously strong!
腕の力半端じゃないから
Hak hits me all the time as well, and his punches really do hurt.
僕もよく殴られるけど ハクの拳はくるよね
なぜかいつも楽しそうだよね ジェハ
You always seem to be enjoying yourself, Jae-ha.
体特別硬いわけでもないね
Your body isn't particularly hard.
肌ふにふにしてるし
Your skin is squishy too.
Zeno's skin is silky smooth.
ゼノの肌はつるすべだから
雷獸の体のがよっぽと硬いよ
The Thunder Beast's body is way harder.
彼奴が黄龍だったていう方が説得力あるね
I'd sooner believe he's the Yellow Dragon.
今まで黙っていたが実は俺黄龍...
I've been keeping it secret,
but I'm actually the Yellow-
其方が龍なら その名は暗黒龍だ
If you were a dragon,
you'd be the evil Dark Dragon!
暗黒龍
The Dark Dragon...
Sounds kind of cool...
其方悔しくないのか
Aren't you upset?!
Sounds kind of cool...
あやつに立場が脅かされておるのだぞ
He's threatening your position!
Remember your pride as a dragon!
龍の誇りを思い出せ
つっててもな...
Yeah, but...
Now, now.
The Yellow Dragon has his own life to live.
黄龍君は黄龍君の人生がある
You're always forcing your values on others.
It's a character flaw of yours.
自分の価値観を他人に押し付けるのは君のよくないところだよ
だが
But...
漸く四龍が古からの兄弟が集まったのだ
the ancient brotherhood of dragons has finally been reunited.
神話の時代から 数千年の邂逅が漸く
Thousands of years after the age of legends,
我等の代で叶ったのだぞ
the prophecy is fulfilled in our generation!
私は...
I...
Weep
Weep Weep
I'm truly moved to have met all of you.
其方等四龍と再会出来たと本当に...
Weep
Weep Weep
分かった分かった
Okay, okay.
Weep
Weep Weep
伝説の四龍が揃った
We have all four of the legendary dragons.
When you think about it, it should be amazing,
考えて見れば凄いことなんだろうけど
but I'm underwhelmed by how easy it was.
あっさりし過ぎて拍子抜けだよ
Weep Weep
Miss...
娘さん
Whump
Uh...
I'll carry that.
持ってあげる
This is pretty heavy.
結構重くね
キジャは片手で軽々よ
Ki-ja carries it one-handed, like it's nothing.
He does what? I can't keep up with that.
なにそれゼノついていけね
でも白龍ってなんかちょっと可愛かった
But the White Dragon is kind of cute.
そうなの
Yeah.
キジャって可愛いのよ
Ki-ja's cute.
皆可愛かった
They're all cute.
娘さんも可愛いね
You're cute too.
I know what the others said.
ユン達はいろいろ言ってたけど
私は貴方が黄龍だと思うわ
Nonetheless, I believe you're the Yellow Dragon.
It's hard to explain,
うまく言えないけど
貴方の纏う空気は普通の人とは違う
but you feel different from ordinary people.
黄金の温かい日だまり見たい
You feel like a warm, golden patch of sun.
初めて会ったけれど
We've never met before, but I feel cheerful being around you.
貴方と居ると 明るくなれるの
Let me properly introduce myself.
ちゃんと言ってなかったから 改めて言うわ
私はヨナ
I'm Yona.
黄龍ゼノ これからよろしくね
It's nice to meet you, Yellow Dragon Zeno.
Heavens, thank you for this day.
天よ 今日をありがとう
今夜は一際 月が綺麗だ
The moon is especially beautiful tonight.
When darkness falls upon the land,
闇 落つる大地
龍の血により再び蘇らん
the dragons' blood will restore life once more.
古の盟約従い 四龍集結せん時
In accordance with the ancient pact, when the four dragons are gathered,
王 守護する剣と盾が目覚め
the sword and shield that protect the king will awaken.
ついに赤き龍 暁より帰り給う
The red dragon will return at dawn.
決めた
I've decided.
行こう
We're going.
ここにその神官様とやらがね
So this priest of yours lives here?
Yun, did you once live here?
ユン君は以前 ここで暮らしてたのかい
Yeah.
まだそんなに経ってないのに
It hasn't been that long, but it feels like I've been gone for years.
何年も帰ってない気がする
イクス 戻ったよ
Ik-su! We're back.
What is this?
何 これ
イクス
Ik-su!
Why?
なんで
Huh?
あれ
ユン君
Yun...
待って 今手当を
Hold on! I'll treat your wounds.
I'm sorry.
ごめん
お腹空き過ぎて 滑って転んじゃった
I was so hungry, I slipped and fell.
Huh?
いやぁ 九死に一生を得ました
Whew. I narrowly escaped death.
Nag
じゃないだろう このバカ神官
You can't be serious, you stupid priest!
Nag
なんで普通に暮らしてて
家めちゃくちゃ餓死寸前転んで大けがだよ
Nag
How do you wreck the house, starve, and hurt yourself falling as a matter of routine?
俺がいなきゃ本当に何も出来ないのな
Nag
Without me, you really are hopeless!
You're a huge pain in the butt!
Nag
めんどくさすぎ
Die and return to heaven!
Nag
一遍天に帰れ
Thank heavens
Yun's shouting!
ユン君の怒鳴り声だ
Thank heavens
You were panicked, and crying too.
ユン君 泣いて取り乱してたもんね
I didn't cry, and I wasn't panicked!
泣いてないし 取り乱してないよ
神官殿
Priest, please forgive our sudden visit.
突然の訪問をお許しください
お会いできて光栄です
It's an honor to meet you.
No, I am honored to meet you.
いえいえ こちらこそ
Ah...
ずいぶん賑やかになりましたね
Your group certainly has grown.
ヨナ姫様も様々な事を経験なされたようだ
You look like you've experienced many things, Princess Yona.
イクス 四龍は揃ったよ
Ik-su, we have all four dragons.
What are the "sword and shield that protect the king"?
王を守護する剣と盾ってなに
王というのはヨナ
Is Yona the king?
それとも現国王スウォン
Or is it the current king, Su-won?
王を守護する剣と盾が現れるには もう少し時間が必要なようです
We'll need some more time before the sword and shield appear.
その時が来たら きっと分かるでしょう
When the time comes, you'll know.
Huh. So it isn't time yet.
今はその時じゃないってことか
Then what should we do now?
じゃこれからどうしようか
どうして皆 本題を避けるの
Why is everyone avoiding the main question?
Miss, what do you want to do
with the four dragons?
娘さん 四龍を集めてどうしたい
Huh?
娘さんとそこの兄ちゃんは城を追われたって事だから
You two were chased from the castle,
so I know you need fighters to survive.
戦力がいるのは分かる 生きる為に
でもそれから先は
But what about after that?
ずっと逃げるだけ？
Will you keep running?
No.
違うわ
No?
違う？
なら
Then will you defeat Su-won, who usurped the throne, and retake Hiryuu Castle and the crown?
王位を簒奪したスウォンを討ち
緋龍城を王座を取り戻そうとお考えか
む 無理だよ 城に攻め込むなんて
W-We can't attack the castle.
いくら四龍がいるなんて この人数じゃ...
Even with the four dragons,
our numbers are insufficient.
出来るか出来ないかじゃない
Whether we can or can't doesn't matter.
I'm asking if that's what she wants to do.
その気があるかどうか だよ
Besides, it isn't impossible to take a single castle...
それに本気で四龍の力を使えば
with the dragons' true strength.
城一つ落とすのも不可能じゃない
No
al
an
nch
t
No
al
an
nch
t
まぁ ゼノにはそんな力ないけどね
No
al
an
nch
t
No
al
an
nch
t
No
al
an
nch
t
Nonchalant
I'm not that strong, though.
Slump
其方は
You little...
新参者がすまぬすまぬ
Sorry, I know I'm new.
別にそうしろって言ったわけじゃないから
I'm not telling you to do that.
I was just wondering what your plan was.
どうするのかなって素朴な疑問だから
ゼノがついて来たのはゼノの勝手だし
Following you was my choice.
娘さんも自由に考えていいから
You're free to come up with your own plan.
それよりゼノお腹空いた
Anyway, I'm hungry!
そなた忙しないな
You never quit, do you?
とりあえず 御飯にっすか
Well, we might as well eat.
飯 飯
Hooray, food!
しかし 驚いたね ゼノ君には
That was a surprise.
まさかヨナちゃんにああいう切込みをするとは
I wasn't expecting Zeno to go after Yona like that.
ああ あの者はどうも掴めぬ
Yes. He's difficult to understand.
姫様はお父上をなくされて まだ日も浅い
It was only recently that the princess lost her father.
She can barely protect herself.
ご自分を守るのがやっとあのお方には
It's too heavy a question for her.
重すぎる問いだった
ただ親の仇をとるだけとは違う
She isn't simply trying to avenge her father.
ヨナちゃんにとっては逆賊でも
Yona sees Su-won as a traitor,
but the rest of the kingdom may not.
国にとって必ずしもそうとは限らない
王座を取り戻すということは この国のすべてを背負うということ
Retaking the throne means taking responsibility for the entire kingdom.
たった十六の女の子に それはあまりにも無謀だ
That's ill-advised for a sixteen-year-old girl.
Hak, you know the king.
ハク そなた王と知り合いだろう
どうのような人物だ
What is he like?
さぁな
Hard to say.
相変わらずスウォンについては何も喋らぬな
He still refuses to speak about Su-won.
Have you noticed?
気づいてる
その名出す度 ハクの顔が少し陰るんだ
Whenever you say that name, Hak's face darkens.
余程憎い相手ということか
He must really hate him.
いいえ
No.
余程情がある相手だったんだよ
He must have been a very dear friend.
いい夜ですね
Pleasant night, isn't it?
Ik-su.
イクス
先程のことを考えておられるのですか
Are you thinking about what he said?
でも 貴方の顔は迷いがないように思えます
However, I see no doubt in your face.
私 初めて城の外の人達と話して
For the first time, I spoke with
people outside the castle.
I walked myself ragged, carrying the weapons my father had forbidden.
父上が禁じた武器を手にボロボロになるまで歩いたの
I heard their bitterness toward the reality
that hadn't changed since my father's rule.
It was mortifying.
悔しかった
もっとも平和を愛する父上の国は幸せではなかったのだから
My father loved peace above all, but his kingdom wasn't happy.
The more I learned, the more powerless I felt.
知れば知るほど 私の力はあまりに弱かったから
でも 必死にてを伸ばしたら 伸ばし返してくれた人がいた
But when I reached out in desperation,
there were people who reached back.
引き上げる力が足りなかったら
I wasn't strong enough to pull myself up, but others pushed me from behind.
後ろから手を貸してくれた人もいた
私はこの国に守りたい人が沢山できた
In this kingdom, I met many people I want to protect.
阿波の領主クムジを討ったこと 後悔していません
I don't regret shooting Kum-ji, Lord of Awa.
あれからずっと考えていたの
Since then, I've been thinking.
高華国にはまだ阿波のような町があるんじゃないかって
There must be other cities
in Kouka Kingdom like Awa.
だから私はこれから大地に立って高華国を見渡し
So I'll stand on the heights, gaze across the kingdom,
and help those crushed by an ill fate!
苦境に押しつぶされる人々を助けたい
Father, forgive me.
父上 お許しください
私は貴方の国を守るため 武器を取ります
I will take up weapons to protect your kingdom.
城に帰るのではなく 今はやるべきことがある
And I'm not returning to the castle.
There's something else I must do.
今はまだ 私にはやるべきことがあるから
There's something I must do.
Ik-su, I think you know this, so I'll tell you.
イクス 貴方には見えてると思うから 言うわ
In Awa, I saw Su-won.
私 阿波でスウォンとあったの
I felt I hated him.
憎いと思った 許せないと思った
I felt I could never forgive him.
But I still couldn't draw that sword.
なのに 剣を抜けなかった
どんなに愚かで理解されずとも
No matter how foolish or incomprehensible, some love cannot be discarded.
捨てられない情は確かにあります
You may try to stop your heart,
unable to forgive yourself,
自らが許せず
心の臓を止めようとしても
また走り出す心に絶望することもあるでしょう
but there will be times when you lose hope because your heart has been moved again.
緋龍王も仰った
King Hiryuu said so himself.
いや 我はもう人間だ
No, I am human now.
Though the humans may hate and betray me,
I cannot help but love them.
人に憎まれ人に裏切られても
人を愛さずにいられないのだ
だからこそ僕は 人が愛しいと思うんです
That is why I love people.
Are you practicing with a sword?
剣の練習ですか
Hak...
ハク
風邪ひきますよ
You'll catch a cold.
岩陰に行きましょう
Let's find shelter by the rocks.
It isn't stopping.
止まねぇな
I hope the river doesn't flood.
川が氾濫しないといいが
怒ってる ハク
Are you mad at me, Hak?
I'm not mad.
怒ってませんよ
少し怖いだけだ
Just a little scared.
私が剣を使うと 危ない目にあうかもしれないから
Because using a sword could put me in danger?
私もハクが危ない目にあうのは怖いよ
I'm afraid of seeing you in danger too.
That's why I don't want to use you as a shield.
だからこそ 絶対にハク盾にしたくないの
昨日ここに来る途中ジェハに言われたわ
On our way here yesterday,
Jae-ha told me something.
You want me to teach you to use a sword?
剣術を教えてほしい 僕に
Hak was angry that I asked and refused.
ハクにはダメだと怒られたから
He said a bow was one thing,
but a sword was too dangerous.
弓はともかく 剣なんて危ないって
成程
I understand.
If I were Hak, I would do everything I could to shield you from danger.
確かに僕がハクなら
自分を盾にしてでも
ヨナちゃんを決して危険に晒したくないけどね
でも
But...
I like the way you struggle to become stronger.
強くあろうと足掻く君は嫌いじゃないよ
そんな君だから 僕もついて来ちゃった訳だけど
That's why I came with you.
"I want you, more than any other, to be safe and happy."
君にはずっと 誰より安全で幸せな場所に居てほしい
それが ハクの本音だと思うけどね
That's probably what Hak thinks.
それはダメよ
That won't do.
You're right.
そうだね
ある意味 君を縛るような言い分だ
In some ways, that restricts you.
本当に どこかに縛っておきたいかも
Maybe he does want to keep you tied up...
どこかに閉じ込めて君を他の男に見せたくない
hidden away where other men can't see you.
なんてね
Just kidding.
見せたくない
Can't see me? Who are you talking about?
誰の話
勿論 君を独占したいハクの話
I'm talking about how Hak wants you all to himse-
Hey!
遅いよ二人共
Hurry up, you two!
はい
Okay!
Crack
あのクソたれ目 殺す
I'll kill that droopy-eyed bastard.
Crack
あのな 姫さん あのたれ目の言うことは
Princess, you shouldn't listen to-
うん 嘘でしょう
Yeah, he's lying.
そんなの分かってるよ
I know that.
ハクが私を他の人に見せたくないとか なんか謎だし
I don't understand why you'd want
to hide me from people.
Yeah, it's a lie.
嘘ですよ
In fact, the opposite is true.
むしろ真逆
俺は見せてやりてぇよ あんたを
I wish I could show you to Mun-deok and King Il.
ムンドクの爺に イル陛下に
あんたを城から追い出したバカ野郎共に
To those idiots who chased you from the castle.
高華国中の民に
To the people of Kouka Kingdom.
見ろ これがヨナ姫だ
Look. This is Princess Yona.
She cut her hair and took up a sword.
髪を捨て 剣をとり
この国を支えんと 誰よりも強く生きている
She works harder than anyone
to support this kingdom.
ヨナ姫は ここにいる ってね
"Princess Yona is here," I'd tell them.
なに らしくないこと言ってるの
What is this? You don't sound like yourself.
ですね
You're right.
忘れてください
Forget what I said.
Too late.
もう遅いわ
忘れない
I won't forget.
ごめんねハク
I'm sorry, Hak.
雨が上がったら 私はまた剣をとるわ
Once the rain stops, I'm taking up a sword again.
雨上がってきた
The rain stopped.
Princess...
姫さん
When did you get here?
何時こちらへおいてに
よろしいのですか 風牙の都は
What about Fuuga?
なに すぐに戻ります
I'll return there soon.
He's still young.
こやつはまだ若い
この老い耄れが教え込まねばならぬことも色々とありましてな
There are still things this old fart has to teach him.
My, my.
それはそれは
頼りにしていますよ 風の新たな部族長殿
We're counting on you, new leader of the Wind Tribe.
Good work in the Earth Tribe territories.
ご苦労でしたな 地の国の件は
What's your next step?
次はどのような企てを
ご自分の目でお確かめください 天の神と共に
See for yourself, along with the gods in heaven.
Crying tears for the days that won't return
modoranai hibi ni namida koboshite
私はまだ何も成し遂げてはいない
I haven't accomplished anything yet.
立ち留まる訳になどいきません
I can't stop now.
この国を生き残られるために
I must keep this kingdom alive.
You look up to the sky, and it's burning bright red
miageta sora ga akaku akaku moeru
Now that you know your own strength and weakness
jibun no tsuyosa yowasa kizuketa no nara ima
私はまだよわい
I'm still weak.
けれど
But...
I don't want to pretend I don't see what's happening around me.
私は見ないふりをして生きるのは嫌だ
父上が愛したこの国を 人々を
誰にも傷づけさせたになんかしない
I won't let anyone hurt the kingdom and the people my father loved.
You should have no fear and go where your heart takes you
kimi yo osoreruna kokoro omomuku mama
力を貸して 皆
Lend me your strength, everyone.
Cleaving through the wind, your path is lit
kaze wo kirisusumu sono tabiji wo
勿論です
Of course.
俺も
Me too.
この天才美少年に任せてよね
Leave it to this handsome genius.
By the dawn
akatsuki ga terasu
ヨナちゃんの頼みとならば
As you wish, Yona.
(Gather, fierce arm)
(tsudoe takeki kaina)
Me too!
ゼノもゼノも
(All-seeing eyes)
(senri no hitomi)
Feet that dash through the sky
sora wo kakeyuku ashi
仰せのままに
As you wish.
(Shield of eternity)
(kuon no tate)
行こう 皆
Let's go!
Fulfill the ancient vows
inishie no chikai ima hatashite
O night, break into dawn
yoru yo akete yuke
Thank you for your support!!